Ningning.
They are from the Huo family.
Don't worry.
Protect yourself.
Shi'an.
Take Siyao and go quickly.
Take her and go first.
I'll cover you.
Shi'an.
Take them and go first.
Lin Jinwen and I will stay.
No.
Siyao.
I have another purpose for being here.
Rule number three of our agreement:
Take them away immediately.
Okay.
Go.
Go quickly.
Go, go quickly.
Hurry up.
Come on, get in the car.
Hurry, get in the car.
Take them away.
Leave it to me.
Young Master.
We're here.
Good.
Brothers.
My father died
at the San Faci Winery.
Come on.
Charge in with me.
Go.
Lin Jinwen.
Don't let them escape.
Especially Thomas.
Lin Jinwen.
Jinwen.
Go, go.
Hurry, hurry.
It's all over.
Catch up with them.
Siyao.
Wake up.
Zhou Wei.
Huo Qishan.
I know you are the real culprit behind the smuggling.
Even the Satanic Society
exists under your indulgence
and tacit approval.
Tell me,
why did you become like this?
For money,
for power,
for the entire Huo family.
You are still young.
You don't understand.
Then do those lives not matter?
The Huo family's status is the most important.
The Huo family's status?
I think it's just your own selfish desires.
Sir.
Sir, bad news.
The St. Faci operation failed.
That kid Lei Zijun
took all the accounts.
They were all handed over to the police.
Now Huang Xianzhong
has sent people to arrest you.
What are you panicking for?
Arrest me?
Let's go.
I will absolutely not go with you.
I know you have feelings for this kid.
If you don't come with me, I'll shoot him.
Don't worry about me.
If you leave, there's really no turning back.
I'll go with you.
Let him go.
Ningning, don't!
Don't go!
Once we are safely out of the city,
I'll let him go.
Huo Qishan,
come back here!
Ningning.
Why did you...
Because he is my dad.
I can't just leave him.
You will be fine.
Don't scare me.
It's okay.
Please,
Reporter Sun.
Don't worry.
Even if I have to risk my life this time,
I will never let the truth sink into oblivion again.
You're awake.
I want to go to Shengfaxi Winery.
Okay.
I'll go with you.
Down with the foreigners!
Give us justice!
What's this nonsense?
Arrest them!
Give us justice!
Commissioner Huang.
What are you doing?
Mayor Zeng,
you have been dismissed.
Please cooperate with the investigation.
Take him away.
Down with the foreigners!
Give us justice!
Commissioner Huang.
Why are you here?
You didn't even notify me in advance.
This way.
Have some tea.
I'm not here for tea.
Then what are you here for?
To catch a lackey.
Your brothers from Xinfeng Stronghold should all be here.
Dad.
Brothers of Xinfeng Stronghold,
Shi'an has avenged you.
For so many years, your wronged souls
have been lingering above.
Now your grievances have finally been redressed.
Rest in peace.
Marshal Duan,
brothers,
rest in peace.
Nephew,
Back then, Marshal Duan
refused to cooperate with them,
which is why he was murdered.
That night, before he came to the winery,
he sent someone with a letter for me.
He said that in this matter,
he would either succeed or die trying.
He also instructed me to tell you and your mother
that if he died,
you should
leave Phoenix City
and never come back.
Marshal Duan
was open and aboveboard all his life.
Even when facing the scum of the Satan Society,
he still wanted
to try peaceful means before resorting to force.
Who knew
he would be murdered?
Sir!
Huo Qishan has escaped.
Don't move.
Don't move!
Where are they?
Huo Qishan is taking Ningning to the UK.
To the UK?
Did he tell you that?
Yes.
After them!
No.
He said he was going to the UK,
probably to divert our attention.
Mr. Li,
please help me mobilize all the drivers
to look for these two people.
Understood.
Notify the police force
to be on standby.
Okay.
Benefactor,
they are here.
Ningning,
eat something first.
Dad is going out to meet someone.
You are not.
No matter what happens,
I will always be your dad.
Chengrui.
Are you here
to arrest me?
I wouldn't dare.
You
have a gun in your pocket.
If you are really here to arrest me
so you can go back and clear your name,
just do it.
Sir,
if you hadn't saved me back then,
when I was wrongly imprisoned,
I would have ended my life.
But today,
I realized something.
Back then,
when I broke into Shengfaxi Winery,
Marshal Duan's men beat me up
and threw me into prison.
Actually,
Marshal Duan was trying to save me.
Otherwise,
the one poisoned by potassium cyanide
and buried under the yellow earth
would definitely be me.
What's wrong?
Do you regret it?
I saved you,
and you've done so much for me.
Do you know what you've gained?
Do you feel wronged?
No.
I chose this path myself,
and I killed those people.
I just have to bear all the consequences.
I bid you farewell here.
Take care, sir.
Have you thought it through?
If you turn back now,
you will surely die.
Siyao treats me as her senior brother,
and has repeatedly advised me to turn back.
Recently, I've seen these young people
sparing no effort in solving cases,
even risking their lives to do so.
I ask myself,
why did I become a police officer back then?
Sir,
let me go.